onlineschools.org 2018-01-30

# Privacy Policy | OnlineSchools.org

Terms of Use and Privacy Policy for Use of OnlineSchools.org (Effective Date 1/15/2016)

Thank you for your interest in OnlineSchools.org, and for utilizing our services and content. This page will discuss our Terms of Use and Privacy Policy, including the kinds of information we collect as well as how we use that information. By using OnlineSchools.org, you are agreeing to the Terms of Use and Privacy Policy.

We generally collect two kinds of information: submitted information and automatic information. Submitted information is the data users voluntarily send us through our web-based forms. This may include name, telephone number, mailing address, and email address, as well any other information that may be required to match users to an education product or service. This helps us provide the information requested by our visitors. Submitted information is stored and shared with schools and other third parties when needed, so that they may give users information about education-related services, schools, and programs.

By submitting this information, you authorize OnlineSchools.org, as well as our affiliated schools and partners, to contact you in accordance with all applicable laws by phone, text messages, email or mail regarding education options or related topics. If you receive email communications from us, a school, or third party, you may unsubscribe through a link in the email. This will remove you from further mailings from that sender.

OnlineSchools.org also collects automatic information. This includes certain types of anonymous information whenever you interact with us, which is used for improvements and for creating a more tailored user experience. We utilize “cookies” to collect anonymous data for analytics, site optimization and for advertising and marketing purposes. Examples of this kind of information include, but are not limited to, your browser version, operating system version, and your IP address. 

By utilizing OnlineSchools.org, you acknowledge and agree that automatic information collected on our website may be shared with schools, affiliated companies, and third parties for the purpose of providing information about degrees, programs and other education-related products and services. You also acknowledge and agree that we retain the right to release any collected information, including personally identifiable information, to businesses providing our company with administration services (such as an email delivery service). Through this action, you grant us, our affiliates, and partners and vendors the right to contact you for a period of time, and relinquish any rights granted to you by the Do Not Call list or other applicable law. Your submission serves as an omission to Do Not Call requirements established by state and federal governments and may exempt us from other applicable laws.

We also retain the right to release your personal information when required to do so by law. For example, we may do this to abide by a subpoena or other legal procedure, when we believe it is necessary to preserve our rights, to ensure the safety of you or others, to explore alleged fraud, to reply to a government or legal request, and/or in the instance that OnlineSchools.org is merging, acquisitioning, or selling some or all of its assets to a third party.

By using this website, you acknowledge that we use cookies and consent to our use of cookies. Cookies are small pieces of data sent from a website and stored in the user’s web browser, including for technical purposes such as web analytics. Our web analytics are primarily performed using Google Analytics, a tool provided by Google, Inc. Advertising cookies do not contain personally identifiable information, but they do permit advertisers to make ads more relevant to the user’s interests. For more information about Google Analytics, check Google’s privacy policy at <https://support.google.com/analytics/answer/6004245>.

We, including activities through services and partnerships with vendors and third-party service providers, may use cookies for:

  * Web analytics such as demographic and other anonymous data for web optimization and other analysis
  * “Lead auditing” to ensure the accuracy, relevance and validity of submitted information
  * Marketing and conversion-tracking cookies for, but not limited to, targeting and optimizing digital ad serving to improve relevance, user experience, and advertising effectiveness

You can remove cookies at any time through your browser settings, though you may need to do this every time you visit OnlineSchools.org. You can also generally opt out of receiving personalized ads from third party advertisers and ad networks that are members of the Network Advertising Initiative (NAI) or that follow the Digital Advertising Alliance’s Self-Regulatory Principles for Online Behavioral Advertising. Do this by visiting the opt-out pages on the NAI website and DAA websites.

Use our contact form for any questions or concerns about this Terms of Use and Privacy Policy.

_It is possible that we will revise our Terms of Use and Privacy Policy in the future if we change our practices. We recommend that you reread this document periodically to stay up-to-date with our practices concerning your privacy and other important information._
